
// ITE EXAM REVIEWER
export const week1Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Program and Project Planning ",
    question:
      "provide the necessary process steps to scope out planning for systems",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "Systems Design",
    question: "to analyze customer requirements",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Software Requirements",
    question:
      "provide a systematic approach to development from multiple resources",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Software Design / Development ",
    question: "systematic approach for the creation of software design",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Software Implementation",
    question:
      "requirement for informal and formal integration testing, PROVIDE ASSURANCE that engineer builds function",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Software Integration",
    question: "is processed through a configuration",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Software and Systems Integration",
    question:
      "provides a consistent approach to effective integration activities",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Software Subcontractor",
    question:
      "roles and responsibilities describe how a program and projects can benefit",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Software and Systems Integration Delivery",
    question:
      "to provide assurance that both software and systems are integrated and working together",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Product Evaluation",
    question:
      "provides the necessary process steps to conduct and perform continuous evaluations",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "Integration",
    question:
      "The act of bringing together smaller components into a single system that functions as one.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    answer: "Software",
    question:
      "A collection of instructions and data that tell a computer how to work.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    answer: "System",
    question:
      "A group of interacting or interrelated elements that act according to a set of rules to form a unified whole",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    answer: "System Architecture",
    question:
      "It is the conceptual model that defines the structure, behavior, and more views of a system.",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    answer: "System Development",
    question:
      "It is the process of defining, designing, testing and implementing a new software application or program.",
  },
];

export const week2Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Program objectives ",
    question:
      "_______identify goals for the program with consideration of how these goals are to be accomplished.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "project managers",
    question:
      "At the senior management level, program and __________ are required to provide effective planning and focus so teams can be effective during software design/development activities.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Communication",
    question:
      "is a positive way for team members to understand your expectations.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Customers",
    question:
      "are best served by creating work products that can be used over a long period of time.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Project Plan",
    question:
      "The term “_________” is used throughout this process area to refer to the overall plan for controlling the project.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Project",
    question:
      "is any undertaking, carried out individually or collaboratively and possibly involving research or design that is carefully planned to achieve a particular aim.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Planning",
    question:
      "is the process of thinking about the activities required to achieve a desired goal. ",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Computer program",
    question:
      "is a collection of instructions that can be executed by a computer to perform a specific task.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Teamwork",
    question:
      "It is an important element in all software programs and projects in order to achieve a common goal or to complete a task in the most effective and efficient way.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Team",
    question:
      "It is a group of individuals working together to achieve their goal.",
  },
];

export const week3Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Objectives",
    question:
      "The _______ of the software architecture are operational scenarios and system or subsystem requirements.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "program and project plans",
    question:
      "The ___________ or schedules are analyzed to determine the impacts on architecture development.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "System ",
    question:
      "is a group of interrelated elements that act according to rules to form a unified whole",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Systems Design",
    question:
      "define elements of a system like modules, architecture, components, and their interfaces and data for a system based on the specified requirements",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "System design",
    question:
      "is the process of defining, developing, and designing systems that satisfy a business or organization's specific needs and requirements.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Engineering Team",
    question:
      "is responsible for developing software requirements, analyzing the system architecture and design, and allocating system requirements.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Scope",
    question:
      "The _______ of the software architecture uses interface requirements to analyze functional designs, software risks and plans to determine the objectives of the architecture.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "System architecture evaluation",
    question:
      "applies to the implementation of enhancements for change or corrections to existing software architectures.",
  },
];

export const week4Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Reuse",
    question:
      "1.	The ______ of software components identifies evaluations by software architecture definitions on how to incorporate components into the software design. ",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "Peer Review",
    question:
      "verification methods identify software bugs, errors, and defects for removal with recommendations to improve code development.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "SCM",
    question:
      "practice involves the identification of systems and software design/development and providing configuration control.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Satisfaction",
    question:
      "4.	One of the key elements for agile software engineering is customer __________.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Lean",
    question:
      "software design/development is more effective for having small working teams across informational handoffs, reducing paperwork loads, and maximizing strong communication.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Software REQUIREMENTS",
    question:
      "are the description of the features and functionalities of the target system.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Agile Methodologies",
    question:
      "support numerous initiatives and provide a program and project with a manager’s approach to emphasize short-term program and project planning.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "CONCURRENT software design/development ",
    question:
      "is a technique to reduce the time to improve productivity through the simultaneous performance of activities and information processing.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "ADAPTABILITY",
    question:
      "9.	Agile involves _________ to changing requirements and close collaboration with customers, and affected teams show accountability.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "System Design",
    question:
      "________ specification defines the components, modules, interfaces, and data to satisfy specified requirements.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "System Design",
    question:
      "is the process of designing elements of a system like modules, architecture, components and their interfaces and data for a system based on the specified requirements.",
  },
];

export const week5Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Agile",
    question: "allows teams to move quickly and adapt to changes easily.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "CM",
    question:
      "methods are a supporting discipline and are not directly involved in creating executable code.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Peer Reviews",
    question: "to eliminate defects and prevent future occurrences",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Technical solution ",
    question:
      "processes support each other and service products related to the software life cycle.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Six Sigma methodology ",
    question:
      "attempts to reduce process variation, resulting in fewer errors and defects",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Software defect",
    question:
      "is defined by customer requirements, whether formally documented or an expectation that is not met.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Data Flow",
    question:
      "analysis and feature breakdown structures ensure fewer opportunities for errors.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Software design/development ",
    question:
      "is a complex process integrated with wastes that include defects as discussed and resulting in rework or reuse",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Lean philosophy ",
    question:
      "The ________ of problem solving uses simple and straightforward tools to achieve fast yet powerful results.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Software Standard",
    question:
      "is a standard, protocol, or other common format of a document, file, or data transfer accepted and used by one or more software developers while working on one or more than one computer programs. ",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "Data-flow analysis",
    question:
      "is a technique for gathering information about the possible set of values calculated at various points in a computer program.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    answer: "Configuration management",
    question:
      "is a process for maintaining computer systems, servers, and software in a desired, consistent state. It's a way to make sure that a system performs as it's expected to as changes are made over time.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    answer: "Agile",
    question:
      "this method allows teams to move quickly and adapt to changes easily.",
  },
];
export const prelimExam = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "RESOLUTION",
    question:
      "Conflicts in requirements, architecture, or program and project plans should be reported to affected product teams for ________",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "Prepare cost evaluation",
    question:
      "Which of the following is NOT a criteria for conducting peer review? ",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "SYSTEM DESIGN",
    question:
      "It is the process of designing the elements of a system such as the architecture, modules, components, etc. ",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "RESULTS",
    question:
      "__________ of software design for architecture changes are examined to determine appropriate design methods to ensure problems are always addressed.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "OBJECTIVES",
    question:
      "__________ of the software architecture are operational scenarios and system or subsystem requirements. ",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Concurrent",
    question:
      "A software design/development method reduces the time to improve productivity through the simultaneous performance of activities and information processing. ",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Program objectives",
    question:
      "identify goals for the program with consideration of how these goals are to be accomplished. ",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "SENIOR MANAGER",
    question:
      "The responsibility of this personnel is to provide the common framework for program and project planning to address engineering tasks. ",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "PROJECT MANAGER",
    question:
      "This personnel is required to provide effective planning and focus so teams can be effective during software design/development activities.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "CONFIGURATION MANAGEMENT",
    question:
      "It is a process for maintaining computer systems, servers, and software in a desired, consistent state. ",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "SYSTEM ENGINEERING PLAN",
    question:
      "It can be written to establish system-level technical reviews that could be conducted for military and aerospace programs and projects.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    answer: "System Engineering Team",
    question:
      "They are responsible for developing software requirements, analyzing the system architecture and design, and allocating system requirements. ",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    answer: "Program and Project Plan",
    question:
      "This process intended to analyzed and determine the impacts on architecture development. ",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    answer: "System Evaluation Plan",
    question:
      "This process aims to provide a common approach to developing the work product architecture. ",
  },
];
